Oh, so you're still waiting
for those two to give the okay.
[TEL]（恵）そっか。
まだ　ＯＫくれないんだ　２人とも。
（倫也）ああ。　やっぱり
クリエーターへの道は険しいな。
Yeah, the road to being a creator is a hard one.
[TEL]（恵）それで　次の締め切りは？
So, when's the next deadline?
（倫也）ゴールデンウイークいっぱい。
それが　ラストチャンスだってさ。
The end of Golden Week.
That's my final chance.
So you only have a few days left.
[TEL]（恵）じゃあ　もう数日しかないね。うっ…。
[TEL]（恵）あっ　でも　まあ
今日から連休だし。
Oh, but we have the next few days off school.
そうだな。　日にちは少なくても
時間は　たっぷりある。
That's right. The days may
be few, but the hours are many.
I just need to start devoting
all my attention to the game!
今日から　ずっとゲームのことだけ考えてればいいんだ。
[TEL]（恵）週明けに
実力テストあるけどね。
There's a proficiency test early next week, though.
それは…　ともかく！
そんなわけだから　また合宿だ！
Right, uh... Anyway, given the situation,
we need another sleepover session!
ミーティングするぞ　加藤。
Come in for a meeting, Katou!
Proposal
No matter what it takes, we need to win those two over
so we can create our ultimate dating sim!
何としてでも　２人を納得させて
俺たちの最強のギャルゲーを…。
Proposal
Oh, sorry, but I can't help out this time.
[TEL]（恵）あ～　ごめん。
私　今回は　参加できない。
えっ　何で？　お前
俺のサークルに入ったはずじゃ…。
Why not? I thought you joined my circle.
[TEL]（恵）まあ　そうなんだけど。
I did, but...
（恵）今　ちょっと　北海道にいてさ。
I'm sort of... in Hokkaido.
[TEL]えっ？
I left today on a family vacation.
（恵）そのう…
今日から　家族旅行で来ててね。
[TEL]いつまで？
（恵）えっと…。→
How long will you be away?
Um, until the end of Golden Week.
ゴールデンウイークいっぱい
ってことで。
[TEL]あ～…　そうですか。
Right.
Whenever we're together in the classroom after school
houkago futari de sugoshita kyoushitsu
You at your desk, just talking and talking on and on
tsukue no ue muchuu de hazumu kimi no koe
You're so dense, and it really shows
donkan na kimi no sono taido ga
And that's why I always have to pick on you
itsumo watashi wo ijiwaru ni saseru no
Sometimes I feel like I'm alone
hitoribocchi da to omou toki mo aru
Some days I can't stop myself from crying
namida tomerarenai hi mo aru
I want you to look and see the real me
hontou no watashi wo mitsumete hoshii no
I'll keep believing that one day you will
kitto tsutawaru to shinjiteiru yo
But you just never, ever, never, ever change, and so
kimi wa itsudatte itsudatte kawaranai kara
I keep sending and sending and sending and sending the same signal
watashi ga nankai mo nankai mo signal okutteageru
Dreaming of the day I'll make it over that hill
yume mita ano oka mezashite
Even when I feel like giving up, I can keep going on
kujikesou na toki mo ganbaresou da yo
Because you're there for me
kimi ga iru kara
All right, let's do this!
Retake the Climax
The deadline's in four days!
よし　やるぞ。
締め切りまで　あと４日。
Absolutely no anime.
絶対に　アニメ見ない。
ゲームしない。
No games, either.
ラノベも読まない。
Not even light novels!
I'll just read one before the final push.
１冊だけ読んだら
最後の追い上げだ。
あれ？
Huh?
ヤベえ　やっちまった…。
Crap. I screwed up.
ハァ…　水　飲んでこ。
I need some water.
（英梨々）あっ　私　コーラ。
Get me a cola while you're at it.
分かったよ。
Sure thing.
An entire day down the drain.
《いきなり
一日　無駄にしちまった…》
《まあ　まだ３日もあるから
大丈夫か》
Well, I still have three days, so I should be fine.
何で　お前が　ここにいる！？
英梨々！
What are you doing here, Eriri?!
（英梨々）
ああ　そっちに置いといて。
Oh, just put it down over there.
原稿　ぬれると困るから。
リアルタイムに困ってるのは→
If it spills on my roughs, I'm screwed.
Well, you letting yourself in here
has screwed my schedule.
勝手に家に上がられてる
俺の方だと思うんだけど。
しょうがないでしょ。
It's not like I had a choice!
Nobody else was going to,
even though I was pressing the doorbell!
いくら　チャイム鳴らしても
誰も出なかったんだから。
いや　そもそも　お前→
That wasn't the point. You haven't
been here at all these past few years.
ここ数年　うちに来たことなんか
なかったろ？
That's because we haven't spoken at all these past few years.
そもそも　ここ数年　ほとんど
話したこともなかったけどね。
Well? I'll ask again.
What are you doing here?
で　あらためて聞くけど
何しに来た？
週末のイベント合わせの
原稿作業に決まってるでしょ。
Working on my drafts for an
event this weekend, obviously.
Don't bring your porno drawings to a guy's house to work on!
男んちに来て　がちの１８禁原稿
描いてんじゃねえよ！
What else could I do?!
しょうがないでしょ！
こっちは　毎月→
I have monthly deadlines,
締め切り　抱えてる身なんだから→
so it couldn't hurt you to be more sympathetic!
そんな薄情なこと
言わなくてもいいじゃない！
それ　どう解釈しても→
Leaving aside your disgraceful
attempts to make me feel guilty,
みっともない逆ギレにしか
聞こえない…　ってのはともかく→
んなもん
自分ちで描けばいいだろ。
surely you can draw that crap at home.
パパが　お客さま呼んで
ガーデンパーティーやってるから→
Dad has guests over for a garden party,
so I came here to get away.
逃げてきたのよ。
部屋に　こもってりゃいいじゃん。
Then just hole yourself up in your room.
If I'd stayed at home, I would've had to put in an appearance.
うちにいたら　顔出さないわけにはいかないのよ！
前の外務大臣とか来てたし。
The former Minister of Foreign Affairs
and whatnot were there.
So the complete disconnect between your
posh life at home and the girl before me now...
そんな　ブルジョアな事情と→
今　ここにいる　お前の姿が
まるで重ならないのは→
仕様ですか？
やかましい。
is intentional?
Bite me.
ところで　進んでるの？
So, have you made any progress?
まだ３日もある。　余裕だ。
I still have three days.
I'll get there.
So you've made no progress whatsoever.
つまり　全然　進んでないのね。
なぜ分かる！？
How did you know?!
When creators use the number of days
they have left as an excuse,
クリエーターが　残りの日数を口にして
言い訳をするときは…。
it's always, without exception,
because they're behind schedule.
一つの例外もなく
作業が遅れているからよ…！
いや　そんな　苦しそうに言うなよ。リアリティーあり過ぎるだろ。
Don't make it sound so painful.
That's way too much reality for me.
もう　諦めたら？
Isn't it time you gave up?
しょせん　あんたに
創作なんて　無理だったのよ。
You don't have it in you to create games.
We don't know that yet!
そんなの分かんないだろ。
I mean, back in the day
we were just as bad as each other.
だって　昔は　おんなじくらい
下手くそだったじゃないか　俺たち。
下手くそな絵　描いて
下手くそな話　付けて→
We'd draw lousy pictures and make up
lousy stories to go with them.
喜んで見せ合ってたじゃないか。
Then we'd happily share them
with each other, remember?
そんな昔のこと　覚えてない。
I can't remember that far back.
それが　今や
そっちは　人気サークルだ。
But despite that, you've become a member of a popular circle.
お前にできたことが
俺にもできないわけがない。
Anything that you can do,
I must be able to do too.
なら　勝手にすればいい。
Have it your way, then.
ああ　勝手にやらせてもらうさ。
Yeah, I will indeed have it my way.
And one day, I'll become a creator so popular that even you won't measure up to me!
そして　いつか　英梨々なんか
目じゃないくらいの→
人気クリエーターになってやる。
まっ　それくらい言い返せるなら
心配するまでもなかったかな。
If you're capable of a comeback like that
then I guess I was worrying about nothing.
心配？
えっ！？　あっ…　いや…。
You were worrying?
Not really.
Hang on, you didn't come here
to motivate me, did you?
もしかして　お前
俺のこと　励ましに？
なっ…　何言ってるのよ
バッカじゃないの！？
What are you talking about?! Are you stupid?!
変なふうに　勘違いしないでよね！
Don't get the wrong idea like some weirdo!
うわ…　何その　におい立つまでに
テンプレートな→
Wow. Nice stinky textbook tsundere reaction.
ツンデレ的　リアクション。
There's no "dere" here!
デレてない！
私は　あんたのことなんか…。
I couldn't care less about—
≪（チャイム）
（英梨々）あっ…。
Who's that?
誰よ！？　こっちは
大事な話の最中だってのに！
We're in the middle of an
important conversation here!
今の大事な話だったんだ。
That was an important conversation?
てか　お前　人んちなのに
フリーダム過ぎるだろ。
And don't you think you're
kind of acting like this is your place?
ぐえ！
ぐえ？
Gueh!
"Gueh"?
どうぞ。　散らかってますけど。
Come on in. Sorry about the mess.
（詩羽）へぇ～　思ったより
片付いてるじゃない。→
This is tidier than I was expecting.
まごうことなき　オタク部屋なのは間違いないけど。
Although you leave no doubt
of this being an otaku's room.
Yeah... Well...
ええ…　まあ…。
Anyway, what brings you here today?
それで　今日は　どうしたんです？
先輩が　うちに来るの
初めてですよね。
This is the first you've ever come to my house.
（詩羽）そうね。
私たち　初めてよね。→
You're right. This is a first for us.
But I'm fine. I'm not
particularly nervous at this point.
でも　大丈夫。　今は　それほど
緊張していないの。→
むしろ
来るべき日が来たというか。→
In fact, I feel as though the time has finally come.
もう逃げ場はないわよ　倫理君
というか。
I feel as though you have
nowhere left to run, Mr. Ethical.
わが家では　お客さまに
心からのおもてなしと…。
The rule in this house
is to treat guests like royalty.
I guarantee you a safe return home!
安全なご帰宅を
保証いたしますから！
なんてね。
I'm just joking around.
ただの陣中見舞いよ。
I only came to visit a soldier at the front.
（詩羽）それで　今の進み具合は
どんな感じ？
So, how goes the battle?
Um, well...
えっと…　その…。
It isn't going. At all.
いえ　まだ　全然。
へぇ～。　もっと女々しく
言い訳するかと思ったけれど→
I was expecting you to make some excuse like a little girl,
but that was a pretty masculine response.
潔いじゃない。
同業者には　そういうのが
通用しないことを→
I learned firsthand quite recently
最近　身をもって　知りましたので。
that such things don't work
on people in the same industry.
There's really no need to
force yourself into this, you know.
別に　無理することなんか
ないじゃない。
詩羽先輩？
Utaha-senpai?
ここで諦めても
今までと変わらない→
Even if you give up, you still have the option of returning
to your former daily routine as a consumer pig.
消費豚としての日常が
待っているだけよ。
それは　倫理君にとって→
And I think that lifestyle
was far from painful for you.
決して　つらい毎日じゃ
なかったと思うのだけど。
それは　そうだけど…。
That may be so...
but I have mixed feelings about
being called a consumer pig to my face.
でも　消費豚って
面と向かって言われると→
何か　もにょります。
ハァ…　だいたい
クリエーターって→
The life of a creator might seem glamorous,
but it's not all wine and roses.
華やかに
見えるかもしれないけれど→
そんなに
いいことばかりじゃないわよ。
そうなの？
ふぅ…。
It isn't?
締め切りは　きついし
競争は　激しいし→
The deadlines are murder,
the competition is rough,
いつ才能が枯れるかも分からない。
and there's no telling
when your talent might dry up.
今を時めく
新進気鋭の若手作家に→
I don't want to hear such cynical talk from
a young up-and-comer at the height of her powers.
そういう　くたびれたこと
言われたくないんですけど。
（詩羽）そして　何より
アンチが　めんどくさい。
And worst of all are the haters.
評価が高ければ　ステマとさげすみ売れなければ　オワコンと笑い→
They deride your good reviews as stealth marketing
and if your work sells poorly, they call you old and busted.
たたきに反応すれば　言い訳とか
自己正当化とか　ほざき→
You can respond to the flame, and they'll say
you're making excuses and rationalizing.
ならばと　何も言い返さなければ
説明責任を果たしてないとか！
But if you just ignore them, they say you're
not fulfilling your responsibility to explain yourself!
あーっ！　あの…なんか→
Those ****ers all deserve to get the banhammer!
粛正されてしまえばいいのに！
ああ…　詩羽先輩　落ち着いて！
Utaha-senpai, calm down!
だから　倫理君。
あなたは　今までどおり→
That's why, Mr. Ethical,
you should continue simply
consuming my works as you always—
私の作品を消費していれば…。
先輩。
Senpai.
Utaha-senpai, do you remember
what you said to me earlier?
詩羽先輩。　この前
俺に　言ってくれましたよね。
You said that I'm unable to envision what I really want to make.
俺には　まだ
自分が作りたいものが何なのか→
見えてないって。
あの言葉　すごく響いたんです。
Those words really got to me.
あのときの俺は
まだ　何も分かってなかったって→
I realized that I didn't really
know anything at the time.
分かったんです。
けれど　だからこそ→
But that's exactly why once
I do see what I want to create,
自分が作りたいものが
見えたときには→
詩羽先輩にも　納得してもらえる
答えが　出せるんじゃないかって→
I think I can probably come up
with what I need to win you over.
そう思うんです。
だから　もう少しだけ
待っててください。
So, wait just a while longer,
必ず　先輩が
納得いくような企画書を→
because I'm going to put together
a project proposal that will gain your approval!
出してみせますから！
（詩羽）そこまで言うのなら
もう止めない。→
If you're that insistent, I can't stop you.
好きにやってみなさい。
ありがとうございます。
Do as you wish.
Thank you!
その代わり
締め切りも延ばさない。
But that doesn't mean I'll extend your deadline.
休み明け　楽しみにしてるわ。
任せてよ！
I look forward to the end of our vacation.
You can count on me!
必ず　詩羽先輩が
参加したいって思うような企画を→
I'll come up with a project
that you'll gladly be a part of!
仕上げてくるから。
（詩羽）じゃあ　そんな倫理君に
もう一つだけアドバイス。
In that case, I have one more
piece of advice to offer you.
何？
What is it?
If you are serious about wanting to form a circle...
もし　あなたが　本当にサークルを
立ち上げたいというなら→
みんなと
ゲームを作りたいというのなら→
and about wanting to create a game with us all,
then I suggest you get all your circle members involved.
メンバー　全員を
引きずり込みなさい。
全員って？
All my circle members?
Without them, you'll never put out
a quality product no matter how hard you try.
でなければ
あなたが　どれだけ頑張っても→
いいものは作れない。
You won't be able to keep
yourself motivated, either.
あなた自身の
モチベーションも保てない。
だから　取りあえずは→
So for now...
今のサークルメンバーだけでも
本気にさせなさい。
you should get the circle members
you do have to want to do their best.
≪（ドアの開く音）
（詩羽）あっ→
Oh, and one more thing.
それから　ついでに　もう一つ。
えっ？
You should have hidden the bicycle as well.
自転車も
隠しておくべきだったわね。
自転車？
それじゃ。
The bicycle?
Until next time.
≪（英梨々）だ～っ！
（英梨々）ハァ　ハァ　ハァ…。→
Kasumigaoka Utaha!
霞ヶ丘　詩羽～！
いや　そこで
呪いの言葉を吐くくらいなら→
If that caused you so much anguish,
maybe you'd have been better off just facing her.
隠れなきゃよかっただろ。
あの女と　あんたの部屋で
鉢合わせなんて　ごめんよ！
No way do I want to bump into that woman here!
どうせ　また
「何でも知ってるわよ」みたいな→
Besides, she'd go "I know what's going on here"
and be all snarky and condescending.
上から目線で
嫌み言われるに決まってるし！
She did know everything
even without bumping into you.
鉢合わせしなくても
全部　知られてたけどな。
Proposal
Huh? What was that?
[TEL]（恵）えっ？　何？
ごめん　よく聞こえなかった。
Sorry, I can't really hear you.
何か　そっち　にぎやかだな。
今どこ？　札幌？
It's sounds pretty noisy over there.
Where are you? Sapporo?
[TEL]えっ？　ああ　えーと…。
まあ　そんなとこ。
Uh, well...
Somewhere along those lines.
楽しんでるか？
Are you having fun?
Yes, lots.
[TEL]うん　すっごく。
そっか。
That's good.
[TEL]それでさ　安芸君。
締め切りの方は…。
So anyway, Aki-kun,
how are you doing with the deadline?
そのことなんだけどさ　加藤。
[TEL]ん？
About that, Katou...
《メンバーだけでも
本気にさせなさい》
Get the members you do have
to want to do their best.
Don't worry about me.
Just focus on enjoying yourself.
お前は
心配せずに　楽しんでこい。
俺一人で
絶対　何とかしてみせるから。
I'll pull something together myself, just you watch.
それじゃあな　加藤。
[TEL]あっ　ごめん　もう一つだけ。
Anyway, I'll let you go, Katou.
Oh. Sorry, one more thing.
何だよ？
Yes?
安芸君ってさ
私のどういうところが　よかった？
What was it about me
that appealed to you, Aki-kun?
[TEL]は？
[TEL]あっ　だからね
こういうことしてたときが→
I mean, did you think anything like,
"It sure was fun when we did that",
楽しかったなぁとか
こういうとこ好きだなぁとか→
or, "I sure love that about her",
逆に　こういうとこが
駄目だったなぁってのでもいいけど。
or even the opposite,
something that you didn't like.
お前　実は　今
不治の病にかかってて→
Have you contracted some fatal disease that'll
keep you from seeing tomorrow or something?
明日をも知れぬ　命だったりする？
[TEL]さすがに　そこまで
劇的な展開はないけど…。→
It's nothing that dramatic.
どうかな？
But was there anything?
そうだなぁ…。
Let me think...
まあ　どれも　楽しかったな。
かなり。
Well, everything with you was fun. Really fun.
[TEL]じゃあ　不満はなし？
Then there's no room for improvement?
でも　まあ　ほんの少しだけ
欲を言わせてもらえれば…。
Well, I guess if there was one thing I could've had differently...
[TEL]言わせてもらえれば？
Go on.
もう少し　息苦しくても
よかったかなって。
Maybe you could've been more overbearing.
[TEL]えっと…　つまり　それって→
Wait, are you saying that you
wanted me to be more mean-spirited?
私に　もっと
意地悪になってほしかったと？
That's not what I meant at all.
全然　違うから。
そんなのは　２人で十分ですよ。
Having those two is plenty enough.
[TEL]ん～　何が違うのかなぁ…。
I'm not sure I see the difference.
Never mind. I'll work something out myself.
[TEL]まあ　いいや。
あとは　自分で考えるよ。
何を？
[TEL]じゃあね　安芸君。
For what?
Talk to you later, Aki-kun.
Title: (Undecided)
Production concept:
Prologue:
Appeal point:
Central character: Heroine A (not yet named)
ああっ　いかん　いかん！
I can't do this.
Title: (Undecided)
Production concept:
Prologue:
Appeal point:
Central character: Heroine A (not yet named)
This LN is Hot!
LN News Blog
まっ　ちょっとだけ。
Well, a short break won't hurt.
Wait...
って！　丸一日　無駄にした！
I wasted another whole day!
Only two days left.
あと２日。
Title: (Undecided)
Production concept:
Prologue:
Appeal point:
Central character: Heroine A (not yet named)
No. That's still plenty of time!
いや…　まだ　十分　間に合う！
Title: (undecided)
アハハ…　ハハハハ…。
Give Up
《俺には
才能なんて　なかった…》
I really don't have any talent.
Give Up
やっぱ　ただの坂じゃん。
It's nothing but a hill, after all.
I thought that maybe coming here would give me some ideas or help me to remember something.
《ここに来れば
何かが思い浮かぶって→
何かを思い出せるって
思ったけれど…》
《今の俺には　何も見えない》
But as I am now, I see nothing.
《満開の桜も　空を舞う帽子も→
Not the blossoms in full bloom,
the hat flying through the air,
坂の上にたたずむ
白いワンピースのヒロインも》
or even the heroine in her white
one-piece dress standing atop the hill.
Is my dream at an end?
《終わるのかな…　俺の夢》
《ここで始まって　ここで…》
Here is where it began.
And here will it end?
kono mama de ikka nanka
Maybe I'll just stay this way
（恵）久しぶり。→
mirai wa mirai no kaze ga fukisou da ne
It feels like the future wind will blow in the future
It's been a while.
また　会えたね。
We meet again.
hajimari no sora wa mikansei
But the sky at the start isn't done yet
（恵）ホント　偶然。　なんてね。
What a coincidence!
Just kidding.
加藤？
Katou?
Oh? You recognize me,
あれ？　私のこと知ってたんだ。
安芸　倫也君。
ai da koi da nanda imantoko
Love and romance are, for me right now
Aki Tomoya-kun!
taigan no jet coaster
Like a roller coaster across the bay
ganbaru yori ganbaru hito wo
I'm not the type to work hard for myself
ouen suru hou ga tokui
Helping others work hard is what I do
お前　これ…。
You're...
flat gimi no mesen no saki ni
Playing out in front of my flat eyes
これ　いったい　何なんだ？
bousoukyou no rhapsody
Is a rhapsody flying out of control
What are you doing?
drama ni naranai real
Reality wasn't cut out to make drama
ねえ　安芸君。
Tell me, Aki-kun...
dou ryouri suru no
How will you cook it up?
ううん　倫也君。
No...
kyara ga yowai toka
You say my character isn't fleshed out
Tomoya-kun, I should say.
あなたが求めていた私は
こんな感じだったかな？
Is this the me that you were hoping for?
iya na anshinkan ga aru da toka
You say you don't like how you can feel relaxed around me
medachitai nante
But I never even once said
In anime, games, and light novels...
アニメの中の　ゲームの中の
そして　ラノベの中の→
ichido mo ittenai yo ne
That I wanted to stand out
あなたの理想の女の子は→
doudemo ii kedo ne
Not that it really matters
is this how your ideal girl talks?
kono mama de ikka nanka
Maybe I'll just stay this way
こんなふうに話して
こんなふうに動いて→
dokka tooku no machi mo aozora nara
If the sky over some faraway town is blue
Is this how she moves?
And...
そして…　こんなふうに
恋に落ちたのかな？
is this how she falls in love?
tachidomaru hi mo nantonaku tanoshii
Even days when we can't progress can be kind of fun
ima wa mada genseki no yume ga
Right now, your dream's still hidden in the rough
合格かな？
えっ？
itsuka kagayakeru nara ii na
But I hope one day you can make it shine
Do I pass?
今の私は　あなたの
作ろうとしている物語の→
Could this me be the heroine
of the story you want to make?
mabushii tte itsuka boyakitai
So that I can complain that it's too bright
ヒロインに　なれるかな？
あなたの力に　なれるかな？
Could she help you?
あっ…　お前　今日まで
北海道だったんじゃ？
I thought you were still in Hokkaido.
ああ　ちょっとだけ
早く　戻ってきたんだよ。
I came home a little early.
えっ？
３日前。
Three days ago.
えっ？
（恵）まさか　連休明けが→
I didn't think they'd make the deadline
the last day of the holiday.
締め切りなんて思ってなくてさ
あ～　まずったなぁって。
I felt like I'd dropped the ball.
まずったなぁじゃねえだろ！
Dropped the ball?!
Why would you skip a family vacation
over something like this?
何で　そんな程度のことで
家族旅行　すっぽかしたんだよ！？
え～　だって　安芸君→
Eh? But Aki-kun,
ここで手伝わなかったら
いつまでも　根に持ちそうだし。
I thought that if I didn't help out,
you'd hold it against me forever.
人を
粘着キモオタみたいに言うな！
Don't make me sound like
some clingy, creeper otaku!
キモオタは　事実だけど。
The creeper otaku part is true, though.
ていうか　それなら
何で　すぐ　顔出さなかったんだよ。
More to the point, why didn't you
come by as soon as you got back?!
Well, even if I'd come in for a meeting,
I wouldn't have been very useful.
だって　どうせ　ミーティングに
私がいても　役に立たないし。
Then why even come back?
なら　帰ってくる意味ねえだろ。
だから　まあ　取りあえず→
Well, I thought that I could contribute to
the circle by providing you with inspiration.
安芸君を励ます方向で
サークル活動してみようかなって。
（恵）あっ　でも
私だけじゃないよ。→
It wasn't all me, though.
澤村さんと　霞ヶ丘先輩も
すごく協力してくれたんだから。
Sawamura-san and Kasumigaoka-senpai
helped me out a lot.
Those two did?
あの２人が？
（恵）この服　澤村さんが
デザインを起こし直して→
Sawamura-san redesigned my outfit
and tweaked it to match your tastes precisely.
きっちり　安芸君の趣味に
合わせてるんだよ。→
She said she was going for
more mini, more flutter, and more 2D.
コンセプトは
「もっとミニに　もっとヒラヒラに→
もっと二次元っぽく」
なんだってさ。
Those don't fit just my taste.
それ　俺の趣味じゃないから。
全ての萌えオタの夢だから。
That's the dream of all moe otaku!
And my manner of speech and performance
（恵）それと
このしゃべり方や　演技は→
were all scripted by Kasumigaoka-senpai.
霞ヶ丘先輩の台本どおり。→
もう　演技指導が
すっごく厳しくってさ～。
Her stage directions were really demanding.
よく耐えたな…。
I'm amazed you survived.
あの人
演劇部で　脚本書いたとき→
She wrote a script for the Drama Club once.
She ended up driving
three members out of the club.
それで　部員を
３人　追い出したんだぞ。
It was pretty fun, though.
それでも　結構　楽しかったよ。
これからも　あの２人と
仲良くやっていけそう。
I think I'll hit it off with those two...
同じサークルの仲間としてね。
as fellow circle members.
加藤…　お前　やる気なのか？
Katou,
are you on board with this?
だから　私だけじゃなくてね。
Like I said, it's not just me.
俺の　適当で　行き当たりばったり
かもしれない夢を→
You believe in my possibly
unrealistic and haphazard dream?
信じてくれるのか？
正直　今は　まだ
安芸君のやろうとしてること→
To be honest, I still have no clue
what it is you're trying to accomplish.
さっぱり　理解できない。
だよな…。
それでも　あなたが　本気で→
Of course.
But even so,
I understand very well that you're dead serious about wanting to make your dream come true.
夢を　かなえたいって
思ってることだけは→
どうしようもなく分かるよ。
加藤…。
Katou...
だから　頑張って　倫也君！
So hang in there, Tomoya-kun!
Make me a heroine whose joy everyone will envy.
私を　誰もが　うらやむような
幸せなヒロインにしてね。
I will, I promise!
ああ　約束する！
I'll turn you into a main heroine
who'll tug at everyone's heartstrings!
お前を
胸が　キュンキュンするような→
メインヒロインにしてやる！
あ～　もうちょっと恥ずかしくない言い方にしてくれると→
Boy, couldn't you have made that
not sound so embarrassing?
ありがたかったんだけどな～。
そんなわけで　今から
ミーティングするぞ　加藤！
On that note, we must convene a meeting immediately, Katou!
何としてでも
２人を納得させて→
No matter what, we're gonna make an ultimate
dating sim that those two will want to get involved in!
俺たちの最強のギャルゲーを
作るんだ！
えっ…　え～　今すぐ？
Right now?!
Damn right!
当たり前だ。
締め切りは　あしたなんだぞ。
We only have one day left!
でも　それって　安芸君の作業が
全然　進んでなかったせいだよね？
But that's your fault for
not getting any work done.
If you have time to nitpick,
you have time to offer ideas!
細かいこと
気にしてる時間があったら→
アイデア出せ。
さっきの演技で　俺にささやけ！
Whisper to me just like you did before!
超萌えさせろ！
Moe me up!
But we have school tomorrow,
and I really need to stop off at home before then.
でも　あした　学校だから
一度　家に帰らなくちゃ…。
安心しろ。　朝の７時までには
解放してやるから。
Not to worry! I'll let you go by 7 AM tomorrow!
え～　女の子には
色々　準備があるんだから→
But girls take longer to get ready.
６時には　帰してよ～。
それでいいんだ！！
Let me leave by 6.
That works too!
ていうか　２話　連続で
同じオチとか　ないわ～。
In fact, it would be wrong to end
two episodes in a row the same way!
（恵）ないのは
安芸君の態度だよ～。
What's wrong is your attitude.
とうとう
巻き込まれちゃったわね。
Looks like we'll end up getting roped into this.
まだ　企画書　完成してないし。
He still hasn't finished his project proposal.
Who knows if it'll be any different tomorrow.
あしたまでに仕上がるか
分かんないし。
（詩羽）メインヒロインが
やる気になっちゃった時点で→
The instant the main heroine
was on board, the battle was won.
勝負あったでしょ。
（英梨々）くっ…。
そんなに悔しかったのなら→
If you're so bothered by it,
perhaps you shouldn't have helped Katou-san.
加藤さんに
協力しなければよかったのに。
はあ！？　何それ。
全然　気にしてない…。
What are you saying?!
I couldn't care—
てか　そういう問題じゃなくて
そもそも　私には関係ないし。
Actually, that's not the issue.
This has never had anything to do with me.
そうやって　肝心なところで
意地を張る　その性格→
If you don't do something about that habit
of being so prideful when push comes to shove,
何とかしないと
いつか後悔するかもしれないわよ。
you might come to regret it one day.
I already do.
（英梨々）もうしてる。
よりにもよって→
I can't believe I'm in a circle together with Kasumi Utako of all people.
あの　霞　詩子と
同じサークルだなんて。
私　実は　結構
楽しみにしてるのよね。
Actually, I'm rather looking forward to working with the Kashiwagi Eri.
あの　柏木エリと組むの。
あたしは　あんたみたいな
へぼ作家の後始末なんて→
I will not be picking up
after a hack author like you!
ごめんなの。
After every good-bye, my cheeks are always warm
bye-bye no ato samenai binetsu
w
And as I feel the wind against them, I always think
yokaze ni fukare kangaeru
Love? Hate? Hate? Love? Over and over
suki kirai kirai suki kurikaesu
What are you seeing in those eyes of yours?
sono hitomi ni utsutteiru no wa
Reality or something 2-D?
real sore tomo nijigen
Don't just say I look pretty like it's no big deal to me
tayasuku kawaii da nante iwanai de yo ne
Tomorrow, you'll rub your eyes and say "good morning"
ashita mo me wo kosutte ohayou wo itte
And talk about all sorts of pointless stuff
tawai mo nai koto takusan oshiete
And as we slowly grow closer together
sukoshizutsu chikadzuiteku kyori ni
What do I do? What am I usually like?
doushiyou jibun ja nai mitai da
This merry-go-round just never stops
merry-go-round ga tomaranakute
Spinning, spinning, the scenery blurs by
mawaru mawaru keshiki ga kawatteku
Like a colorful dream
colorful na yume wo miru
Throb, throb, I can feel them inside
dokudoku shite karadajuu wo
Going 'round and 'round, these feelings
meguru meguru kimochi
I still can't put them into words
mada kotoba ni dekinakute
Even though one word would be enough
hitokoto sore de juubun nanoni
Game Project Proposal 3rd Draft
Regardless of what anyone
else says, this scores zero.
誰が何と言おうと　０点。
Wait just a minute!
ちょっと待って！
今回　相当　自信あるんだけど！
I'm sure this one was a big improvement!
ただ　お目当てのヒロインと
イチャイチャしたいっていう→
All I see in this is your unsightly desire to make out with your ideal heroine.
あんたの醜い欲望しか見えない。
You're the one who told me to
show you what I want this game to be!
自分が作りたいものを
見せろって言ったじゃん！
あまりにも露骨過ぎるのが
腹立たしい。
Something so blatant is nothing but annoying.
I poured my heart and soul into this!
超力作なんだよ！？
I stayed up all night to finish it.
昨日　徹夜で書き上げた
魂の企画書なんだよ！？
It's the project proposal of my soul!
知ってるけど
あんたの態度が気に入らない。
I know that. Your attitude's what I don't care for.
It wasn't just me!
Katou worked her heart out too!
俺だけじゃなくて
加藤だって　頑張ったんだ。
おい　お前も　何か言って…。
Hey, can't you say anyth—
って…　寝るな！
Don't fall asleep!
If anything, since you're a heroine,
you should sleep on your man's shoulder!
いや　ヒロインなら
男に　もたれ掛かって寝ろ～！
Ow! Hey! Wha—
いっ…　痛っ…　ちょっ！
やめ…　やめて！
Cut it—
Ow!